ILGWU. Irwin Solomon papers, 5780/187
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pacific Investment Management Company: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1996-1998 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Glickenhaus and Company: ILGWU Death Benefit Fund, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Goldman Sachs: UNITE General Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE General Fund Third Quarter, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- UNITE Strike and Defense Fund, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: UNITE Staff Retirement Plan, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- S. Rothchild and Company, 1988-1997 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Schroders, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- UNITE General Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Marco Consulting Fund Reports, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- UNITE Staff Benefits, 1995-1997 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Klein and Company [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1994 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Klein and Company [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1994 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico: Jose Torres, Barranquitas, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico: Arbitration, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico: District Court, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Klein and Company: Reports, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Klein and Company: Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Crystal Brands, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Crystal Brands, 1989-1994 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Crystal Brands, 1990-1994 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Crystal Brands: Restructuring, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Crystal Brands: Union Contract, 1982-1988 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Crystal Brands: Izod, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Crystal Brands: Ship'n Shore Shutdown, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Crystal Brands: Agreements, 1987-1990 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Barranquitas: Ratified Agreement, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Barranquitas: Collective Bargaining, 1995-1998 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Barranquitas: Contract Agreements, 1995-1998 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Barranquitas: Correspondence [folder 1 of 3], 1992-1995 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Barranquitas: Correspondence [folder 2 of 3], 1992-1995 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Barranquitas: Correspondence [folder 3 of 3], 1992-1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Bank: Transaction Reports [folder 1 of 4], 1984-1986 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank: Transaction Reports [folder 2 of 4], 1984-1986 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank: Transaction Reports [folder 3 of 4], 1984-1986 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: Transaction Reports [folder 4 of 4], 1984-1986 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1984 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1984 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1984 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1984 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1984 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1984 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1985 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1985 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Bank: Fund Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1985 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Bankers Trust Company: Portfolio Proposal, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  February 25
- Bankers Trust Company: Transaction Highlights, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Delaware Investment Advisors, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Lehman Management Company: Proposal, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  February 26
- Stratford Advisory Group: Suggestions and Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Stratford Advisory Group: Comparative Analysis, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Stratford Advisory Group: Reports, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  September - December
- Stratford Advisory Group: Fund Managers Analysis, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  January
- Stratford Advisory Group: Investment Policies, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- T. Rowe Price: Presentation, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- T. Rowe Price: Investment Summary, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Liquidated Damages, 1985-1987 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Liquidated Damages, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Local 10, 1986-1991 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Local 23-25, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Local 23-25: Arthur Silverstein (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Local 89-22-1, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Local 89-22-1: Sam Byer, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Local 91 Realty Corporation, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Local 99, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Local 99: Domsey, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Local 155, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Local 155: Donnenfeld, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Mutual Redevelopment, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- National Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- National Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- National Retirement Fund, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- New England, 1990-1992 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- New Jersey, 1989-1990 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- ORT, 1991-1992 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Professional and Clerical Employees (PACE), 1990-1991 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Political, 1988-1992 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Research [folder 1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Research [folder 2 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Research: Herman Starobin, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Susan Cowell, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Donald Fischer, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Retiree Services, 1989-1991 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Southeast, 1986-1993 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Southeast: Trial Balance, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Staff Seminar, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  February 1-3
- Towers Perrin, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Towers Perrin, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Union Health Center, 1989-1992 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Union Label, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Upper South, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Upper South: Misty Harbor, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Washington Office, 1988-1991 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Welfare Funds Control, 1988-1992 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Welfare Funds Control: Seminar, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Western States, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 3], 1992 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 3], 1992 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Jay Mazur [folder 3 of 3], 1992 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1991 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1991 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Perry Parker [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Perry Parker [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Finance Reports, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Northeast Department, 1991-1993 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Northeast Department: Sol Hoffman, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Northeast Department: Hazleton Merger, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- New Jersey Region, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Region: Fairfield Textile, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Region: Complaint, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- New Jersey Region: Office, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Midwest Region, 1986-1994 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Midwest Region: Chicago, 1993-1994 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Local 23-25, 1991-1993 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Local 62-32, 1987-1993 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Local 62-32: Mazur-Lopatin, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Staff Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1993 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Staff Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- T and M Security Service, 1986-1993 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Ark Asset Management, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Auditing Department, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Auditing Department: Lloyd Goldenberg, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Benefits, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Central States, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Central States: Paul Winslow, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Deborah Hospital Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Eastern States, 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  February 4-8
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  September 17-21
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  December 15
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  January 25-30
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  May 17-21
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  September 28-30
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT), 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Education Department, 1990-1993 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Engineering Department, 1989-1991 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Health and Safety Department, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Histadrut, 1991-1993 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- National Retirement Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- National Retirement Fund: Staff Orientation, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Local 99, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Local 99: Tracy Smith, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Local 155, 1991-1993 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- National Retirement Fund, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Professional Employees, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Solomon: Personal, 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Solomon: Personal, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Itzhak Omessi, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center: Tuberculosis Project, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Union Health Center, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center: Staff Retirement Fund Meeting, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  December 9
- Union Health Fund: Staff Orientation, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  June 18
- Union Health Services Plan, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Upper South Department, 1992-1993 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Welfare Funds Control Department, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Western States [folder 1 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Western States [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1993 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Western States: Steve Nutter, 1992-1993 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Work in America Institute, 1991-1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Port Authority, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Urban Development Corporation (UDC), 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Bronx Project, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- James Parrott, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation, 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1986-1992 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Lloyd Sportswear Quality Project: Weintraub, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Assembly Ways and Means, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Industry Development Working Group, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Harvard Center for Apparel and Textile Research, 1990-1992 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Garment Center Reinforcement Project, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Messinger's Council on Manufacturing, 1990-1992 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- James Parrott, 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 2], 1993 (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- David Melman, 1989-1994 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- John Newman, 1989-1994 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Burt Conley, 1989-1991 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Perry Parker [folder 1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Perry Parker [folder 2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Lawrence Kleinman [folder 1 of 2], 1993 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Lawrence Kleinman [folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Lawrence Kleinman, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 2], 1994 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Election [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Election [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 1 of 6], 1992 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 2 of 6], 1992 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 3 of 6], 1992 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 4 of 6], 1992 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 5 of 6], 1992 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Official Returns of Delegates [folder 6 of 6], 1992 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Sol Chaikin, 1986-1991 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Chick Chaikin-Robert Lord, 1989-1990 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Susan Cowell [folder 1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Susan Cowell [folder 2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Max Zimny, 1985-1993 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1992 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1992 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Irwin Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1992 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- American Labor Museum, 1975-1997 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Benefit Funds, 1991-1997 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Staff Retirement, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Staff Retirement, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Retiree Service Department, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- UNITE Staff Retirement Plan, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  November 21
- General Executive Board (GEB): Meeting, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  May 17-19
- National Retirement Fund, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  December 12
- Finance Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- National Retirement Fund: Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- National Retirement Fund: Reports, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- National Retirement Fund: Reports, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- National Retirement Fund: Investment Performance Review, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- National Retirement Fund: Meeting, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  December 11
- Health Services Plan: Meeting, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  October 6
- National Retirement Fund: Meeting, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- National Retirement Fund: Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Health Services Plan: Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- National Retirement Fund: Tax, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- National Retirement Fund: Withdrawals, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- National Retirement Fund: Valuation, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- National Retirement Fund: Reports, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Benefits, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Benefits, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Benefits, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- National Retirement Fund: Valuation, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Office Employees Retirement Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- UNITE Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- UNITE Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 95, Folder 6)